{
    "id": "93cb2f2955f34923ba1eb16b69b87c81",
    "title": "They, them, their, theirs exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "7228f6c58ba14d7487dec135efca4b4f",
            "title": "They, Them, Their, Theirs",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "It took ………………….. an hour to finish the work.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "they",
                        "them",
                        "their"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You solve our problems and I will solve ……………………",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "their",
                        "theirs",
                        "them"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I was upset with both of ………………………",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "they",
                        "them",
                        "their"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Have you heard of ………………… ?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "they",
                        "them",
                        "their"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Are ………………… coming with us?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "they",
                        "them",
                        "their"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "It was very kind of ……………………… to help the poor old widow.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "they",
                        "them",
                        "their"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Did you speak to ………………………?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "they",
                        "them",
                        "their"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Did …………………. see you?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "they",
                        "them",
                        "their"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Have ………………… been invited?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "they",
                        "them",
                        "their"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Ask …………………. if they can help?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "they",
                        "them",
                        "their"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}